. .
The walls are cold, the air is thin The noise
outside is closing in A single light, a buzzing
sound Another day in the underground
I'm running from the face I see The victims say
they made of me The wholesome girl so sad and worn
A David for their Goliath scorn This rage is just
a heavy stone The gravity I've outgrown
Shedding skin, shedding weight Escaping from
this world of hate They loved the trial, the
family torn They loved the story, a new star born
But not from music, not from grace From the hot
chocolate drinking angel's face The shark was
right, the nuke went off We won the battle, but at
what cost? We're radioactive, will it teach us?
We're just the joke the victim said
I'm trapped inside this wilderness.
This fortress built on bitterness.
This isn't freedom. This is a cell. This
righteous hell. This righteous hell.
I see a signal in the endless black A single
light, no one's turning back The pull of the old
world fades away
A new day The countdown's running in my head
Ignoring all the things they said The engine
roars, a crimson light A pillar of fire in the
night The pressure builds, I'm pinned to the
seat My heart is pounding with the beat The G4 is
pulling a heavy stone The last chain breaks, I'm
not alone
I'm climbing, climbing Past the point of no
return I'm flying, flying With the fire I let
burn Just a signal, a distant light Burning
through the endless night Adastra, Adastra
I'm so, so, so scared.
The sky is tearing at the seams Awake now from
their broken dreams The stardust is just a trail
of dust The stardust is the thing I trust The
clouds are falling far below A place of pain I
used to know The blue gives way to endless black
There is no thought of turning back I'm
climbing, climbing past the point of no return.
I'm flying, flying with the fire I let burn. Just
a signal, a distant light, burning through the
endless night. Anastro.
Anastro. I'm
And now the engines of the silence is a holy sound
The rage is gone, the fear is lost in this new
universe I found That cage is just a distant
star, a tiny light I left behind I finally know
just who you are, the other half of my own mind
I'm loved
by the sun I'm held by the void An orbit just begun
A life not destroyed I'm loved by the moon I'm
cradled by the black My heart is back in tune
There is no turning back
And the stars
are singing A song of love and space
I'm finally, finally reaching for you
I see the colors of the nebula, a place I've only
seen in dreams. The reds, the blues, the purples
call, flowing in majestic streams.
This is the place I was meant to be. This is the
stardust that is me. The cosmos and the rockets
fire my one, my only true desire.
Love by the sun.
Yai, yai, yai, yai, yai, yai, yai, yai, yai, yai,
yai, yai, yai, yai, yai, yai, yai, yai, yai, yai,
yai, yai, yai, yai, yai
The walls are gone, the air is clear There is no
noise, there is no fear The stardust is a
forgotten ghost The engine has delivered me to
the coast Of a new world, a new shore A place I've
never been before The cage is broken, the
victim's saying his thoughts
Ooh, clean script is in my head The friction
burned away in the fire Leaving only my truth to
deserve.
I'm
loved by the sun I'm held by the void My orbit has
begun
is not destroyed
Sedestra, sedestra,
sedestra